{"responseData":
	{"feed":
		{"feedUrl":"http://www.rollingstone.com/music.rss",
		"title":"RollingStone.com: Music",
		"link":"http://www.rollingstone.com/music",
		"author":"",
		"description":"Music from Rolling Stone",
		"type":"rss20",
		"entries":[
			{"title":"Coldplay Salute WWI Veterans in 'All Your Friends' Video",
			"link":"http://www.rollingstone.com/music/videos/coldplay-salute-wwi-veterans-in-all-your-friends-video-20141109",
			"author":"",
			"publishedDate":"Sun, 09 Nov 2014 08:57:00 -0800",
			"contentSnippet":"With the UK set to celebrate Remembrance Sunday to commemorate those who served in the British and Commonwealth ...",
			"content":"With the UK set to celebrate Remembrance Sunday to commemorate those who served in the British and Commonwealth military, Coldplay have released a video for their Ghost Stories bonus track \"All My Friends\" based solely on archival footage from World War I.\n\nThe band does not appear in the video, focusing instead on wartime images both banal......",
			"categories":[]},
			
			{"title":"Willie Nelson: Obama 'May Be Happy' With Weed Legalization","link":"http://www.rollingstone.com/culture/news/willie-nelson-obama-may-be-happy-with-weed-legalization-20141108","author":"","publishedDate":"Sat, 08 Nov 2014 05:57:00 -0800","contentSnippet":"Willie Nelson visited the White House this week to perform in a salute to the troops, but the noted marijuana enthusiast said ...","content":"Willie Nelson visited the White House this week to perform in a salute to the troops, but the noted marijuana enthusiast said beforehand that he wouldn't be bringing up the topic of legalization. As he told CNN, that was partially because he felt that he and President Obama were on......","categories":[]},{"title":"Taylor Swift Pulled Music From Spotify for 'Superfan Who Wants to Invest,' Says Rep","link":"http://www.rollingstone.com/music/news/taylor-swift-scott-borchetta-spotify-20141108","author":"","publishedDate":"Sat, 08 Nov 2014 05:56:00 -0800","contentSnippet":"Taylor Swift's decision to remove her music this week from Spotify is a \"big fist in the air\" that other prominent artists are ...","content":"Taylor Swift's decision to remove her music this week from Spotify is a \"big fist in the air\" that other prominent artists are sure to follow, says her longtime record label president.\n\nIn the week she sold 1.3 million copies of her new album 1989, Swift abruptly pulled her single \"Shake It Off\" and......","categories":[]},{"title":"Q&A: Dave Grohl on Austin's Musical Wizards, Gentrification","link":"http://www.rollingstone.com/music/news/q-a-dave-grohl-on-austins-musical-wizards-gentrification-20141108","author":"","publishedDate":"Sat, 08 Nov 2014 05:41:00 -0800","contentSnippet":"For the fourth episode of the Foo Fighters' musical travelogue Sonic Highways, Dave Grohl and Co. headed to Austin, Texas ...","content":"For the fourth episode of the Foo Fighters' musical travelogue Sonic Highways, Dave Grohl and Co. headed to Austin, Texas Friday night to explore the history and culture of, as Grohl put it, \"some of the weirdest, freakiest stuff in the city that inspires people all over the world.\" Delving into everything......","categories":[]}]}},"responseDetails":null,"responseStatus":200}